[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Do you think that you were acting legally?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "you", "were", "acting", "legally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "In what you were doing?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "And why is that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, it was my stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "my", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "``", "RB", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 71, "question": "So when the judge at the arraignment says, how do you plead to kidnapping, how do you plead to rape and whatever else, what are you going to say?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "the", "judge", "at", "the", "arraignment", "says", ",", "how", "do", "you", "plead", "to", "kidnapping", ",", "how", "do", "you", "plead", "to", "rape", "and", "whatever", "else", ",", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "It definitely is going to be two words, \"not guilty.\"", "answer_tokens": ["It", "definitely", "is", "going", "to", "be", "two", "words", ",", "``", "not", "guilty", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "And, again, that begs the question, well, what kind of circumstances could possibly justify all that, showing that you love your daughter?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "again", ",", "that", "begs", "the", "question", ",", "well", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "circumstances", "could", "possibly", "justify", "all", "that", ",", "showing", "that", "you", "love", "your", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "And in terms of where this is going to go, it's going to come down, presumably, to his word against his former attorney's word, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", "of", "where", "this", "is", "going", "to", "go", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "come", "down", ",", "presumably", ",", "to", "his", "word", "against", "his", "former", "attorney", "'s", "word", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Well, what was his advice to you regarding the entire plan?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "was", "his", "advice", "to", "you", "regarding", "the", "entire", "plan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "That if they didn't give me the stuff, you have to call the police.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "if", "they", "did", "n't", "give", "me", "the", "stuff", ",", "you", "have", "to", "call", "the", "police", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Did you have any understanding whether you could detain people or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "understanding", "whether", "you", "could", "detain", "people", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Not until the police came.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "until", "the", "police", "came", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "You can demand your property?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "demand", "your", "property", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Well, are you having any alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "are", "you", "having", "any", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "And how much were you drinking, if you can remember?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "much", "were", "you", "drinking", ",", "if", "you", "can", "remember", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, you know, I had a joke that my doctor says I should never have an empty glass is what I would tell the waitress.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "a", "joke", "that", "my", "doctor", "says", "I", "should", "never", "have", "an", "empty", "glass", "is", "what", "I", "would", "tell", "the", "waitress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you make of seeing him finally give evidence?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "seeing", "him", "finally", "give", "evidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, he's not a bad witness.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "a", "bad", "witness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Is that likely?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "likely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Would you agree with all that, Gloria?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "all", "that", ",", "Gloria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "LORIA ALLRED, CIVIL RIGHTS ATTORNEY: Well, I mean, first of all, I think that's insulting to the judge who is the one who sentenced him.", "answer_tokens": ["LORIA", "ALLRED", ",", "CIVIL", "RIGHTS", "ATTORNEY", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "insulting", "to", "the", "judge", "who", "is", "the", "one", "who", "sentenced", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Tell me this, I mean, talking of behavior involving attorneys, I was pretty shocked by the tone that Ariel Castro's attorneys -- were you shocked?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "this", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "talking", "of", "behavior", "involving", "attorneys", ",", "I", "was", "pretty", "shocked", "by", "the", "tone", "that", "Ariel", "Castro", "'s", "attorneys", "--", "were", "you", "shocked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I was shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Should she should be?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "she", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Exceptional cruelty is what they found or special cruelty.", "answer_tokens": ["Exceptional", "cruelty", "is", "what", "they", "found", "or", "special", "cruelty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "It's looking -- if the jury goes this stage of saying, yes, we do think she is eligible for it, aren't they more likely to say we think she should have it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "looking", "--", "if", "the", "jury", "goes", "this", "stage", "of", "saying", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "do", "think", "she", "is", "eligible", "for", "it", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "more", "likely", "to", "say", "we", "think", "she", "should", "have", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Well, if you think that the IRS commissioner should be fired, do you think that the president of the United States, George W. Bush, should have been fired for acting on faulty intelligence and sending troops to -- the Iraq War?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "think", "that", "the", "IRS", "commissioner", "should", "be", "fired", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "George", "W.", "Bush", ",", "should", "have", "been", "fired", "for", "acting", "on", "faulty", "intelligence", "and", "sending", "troops", "to", "--", "the", "Iraq", "War", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I like that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS", "United States"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"], "PERSON": ["George W. Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "And Alan?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Alan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Similar question.", "answer_tokens": ["Similar", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "How do we make sure the IRS is taken out of politics?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "make", "sure", "the", "IRS", "is", "taken", "out", "of", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "These are great questions.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "great", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Why has he had had to go, when from what I hear, he wasn't actually running the IRS when all this went one?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "he", "had", "had", "to", "go", ",", "when", "from", "what", "I", "hear", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "actually", "running", "the", "IRS", "when", "all", "this", "went", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "You ask the money question.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ask", "the", "money", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Where is that going?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "that", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, it's going further than it would have a couple of days ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "further", "than", "it", "would", "have", "a", "couple", "of", "days", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Dana?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Absolutely agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Excellent.", "answer_tokens": ["Excellent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "When you look at these three scandals in totality, are they real scandals or are they run of the mill issues that any White House has to deal with?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "these", "three", "scandals", "in", "totality", ",", "are", "they", "real", "scandals", "or", "are", "they", "run", "of", "the", "mill", "issues", "that", "any", "White", "House", "has", "to", "deal", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, one is bad.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "is", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Twain"]}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you believe that, given all of the e-mails that have come out today?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", ",", "given", "all", "of", "the", "e-mails", "that", "have", "come", "out", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "UMSFELD: I think the way to think of it is that, as I think Mark Twain said, trust leaves on horseback and returns on foot.", "answer_tokens": ["UMSFELD", ":", "I", "think", "the", "way", "to", "think", "of", "it", "is", "that", ",", "as", "I", "think", "Mark", "Twain", "said", ",", "trust", "leaves", "on", "horseback", "and", "returns", "on", "foot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, I would count them as kind of as undecided.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "count", "them", "as", "kind", "of", "as", "undecided", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Are you suggesting that people, either Hillary Clinton or President Obama, have lied about this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "suggesting", "that", "people", ",", "either", "Hillary", "Clinton", "or", "President", "Obama", ",", "have", "lied", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "No, I'm saying that what's happened is there have been different stories coming out.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "saying", "that", "what", "'s", "happened", "is", "there", "have", "been", "different", "stories", "coming", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Otherwise it's supposition, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Otherwise", "it", "'s", "supposition", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1962"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Can that ever be justified under the First Amendment, never mind anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "that", "ever", "be", "justified", "under", "the", "First", "Amendment", ",", "never", "mind", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I've been in and out of government since 1962, when I was elected to Congress.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "in", "and", "out", "of", "government", "since", "1962", ",", "when", "I", "was", "elected", "to", "Congress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "So it's wrong?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "UMSFELD: I said -- one of my rules is, if you don't know, say you don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["UMSFELD", ":", "I", "said", "--", "one", "of", "my", "rules", "is", ",", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "say", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Is there something so bad that it might cause government to do something like that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "something", "so", "bad", "that", "it", "might", "cause", "government", "to", "do", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Or, as I suspect, is the potential person who leaked it so important and so high up the food chain, they've got to find out who it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", ",", "as", "I", "suspect", ",", "is", "the", "potential", "person", "who", "leaked", "it", "so", "important", "and", "so", "high", "up", "the", "food", "chain", ",", "they", "'ve", "got", "to", "find", "out", "who", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Why do you call this the Grill?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "call", "this", "the", "Grill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Because I like to grill people on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "like", "to", "grill", "people", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Was he right, the president, to fire the acting chief of the IRS?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "right", ",", "the", "president", ",", "to", "fire", "the", "acting", "chief", "of", "the", "IRS", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Should there be more heads rolling?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "there", "be", "more", "heads", "rolling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I think some people may end up going to jail.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "some", "people", "may", "end", "up", "going", "to", "jail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Do we know enough yet?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "know", "enough", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Should Eric Holder consider his position, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "Eric", "Holder", "consider", "his", "position", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "UMSFELD: Oh, I have no idea about that.", "answer_tokens": ["UMSFELD", ":", "Oh", ",", "I", "have", "no", "idea", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric Holder"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "If it turns out that the president has lied about Benghazi, or about the IRS, for example, if it turns out senior White House officials knew more than they're saying about what was going on and the original idea to target the Tea Party came from then -- these are pure hypotheticals, how serious would that be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "turns", "out", "that", "the", "president", "has", "lied", "about", "Benghazi", ",", "or", "about", "the", "IRS", ",", "for", "example", ",", "if", "it", "turns", "out", "senior", "White", "House", "officials", "knew", "more", "than", "they", "'re", "saying", "about", "what", "was", "going", "on", "and", "the", "original", "idea", "to", "target", "the", "Tea", "Party", "came", "from", "then", "--", "these", "are", "pure", "hypotheticals", ",", "how", "serious", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "UMSFELD: I think that the currency a president or leader has is trust.", "answer_tokens": ["UMSFELD", ":", "I", "think", "that", "the", "currency", "a", "president", "or", "leader", "has", "is", "trust", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS", "White House"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "What did you make of the Rumsfeld rule that Joyce gave us there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "the", "Rumsfeld", "rule", "that", "Joyce", "gave", "us", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Well, her father told me that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "her", "father", "told", "me", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rumsfeld", "Joyce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "That I felt that way?", "question_tokens": ["That", "I", "felt", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Can you share one with me?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "share", "one", "with", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Well, sure, I've argued with presidents, I've argued with people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "sure", ",", "I", "'ve", "argued", "with", "presidents", ",", "I", "'ve", "argued", "with", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Do you have any regrets about the way Iraq is today?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "regrets", "about", "the", "way", "Iraq", "is", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "You know, of course you do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "of", "course", "you", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Are they?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Oh, you bet your life.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "bet", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "In \"Rumsfeld's Rules,\" what rule would you have for me?", "question_tokens": ["In", "``", "Rumsfeld", "'s", "Rules", ",", "''", "what", "rule", "would", "you", "have", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ",", "''", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Well, I thought about that coming over here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "about", "that", "coming", "over", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]